CÉSAR MOLTÓ MORILLA

GRAPHICS & GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER

ABOUT ME

I am a programmer specialized in Graphics and Gameplay Programming who loves creating interactive experiences that players find immersive, intuitive and visually impressive.

I am passionate about technology, sports and travelling. When I am not working or studying, I like playing competitive video games, watching movies, and doing outdoor sports and martial arts.

SKILLS

C / C++ / C# / JAVA / GLSL / BLUEPRINTS (UE4 VISUAL SCRIPTING)

UNREAL ENGINE 4 / UNITY 3D / OPENGL / VISUAL STUDIO / ANDROID STUDIO

GRAPHICS PROGRAMMING / GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMING / VR PROGRAMMING

GIT / MERCURIAL / PERFORCE

TEAM WORK / AGILE METHODS / PROJECT MANAGEMENT

LANGUAGES

SPANISH

Native Proficiency | Mother tongue

ENGLISH

Professional working proficiency | C1

GERMAN

Elementary Proficiency | A2

JAPANESE

Elementary Proficiency | N5

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

EMAIL

cmoltomorilla@gmail.com

WEBSITE

https://cesarmolto.github.io

PHONE NUMBER

+34 620 893 530

LINKEDIN

César Moltó Morilla

EDUCATION

REY JUAN CARLOS UNIVERSITY

SPAIN

Master in Computer Graphics, Games and Virtual Reality 2021 - Present

UNIVERSITY OF ALICANTE

SPAIN

Multimedia Engineering Degree, GPA: 7.90 / 10

2016 - 2021

• GPA: 7.90 / 10

ATHLONE INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

IRELAND

Software Engineering Exchange Year (Erasmus K103)

2018 - 2019

• GPA: 8.93 / 10

WORK EXPERIENCE

HANDY GAMES

WÜRZBURG, GERMANY

Game programmer

September 2020 - May 2021

- Worked on the porting of a AAA Action-RPG video game to the Android and IOS platforms.
- Implemented of game controller support, rendering of controllerspecific 3D/2D graphics, and rendering of UI elements and animations.
- Performed graphics rendering optimization, testing and troubleshooting for graphics and gameplay bugs as well as ensuring correct documentation.

4FREAKSFICTION

REMOTE

Game programmer

October 2018 - September 2020

- Worked as volunteer programmer on the development of several video game prototypes for pc and mobile platforms with Unity3D.
- Coordinated code remotely with other programmers to prototype and implement new gameplay features; i.e., combat and interaction mechanics, player controls, etc...

PROJECTS

DODGEBALL MASTERS

Gaphics and gameplay programmer, and Project Manager

2019 - 2020

Supervised and programmed a dodgeball multiplayer game with 8 playable characters and +20 unique skills using C++ and OpenGL.

More information: https://cesarmolto.github.io/dodgeball-masters.html

BATTLE TANK

Solo project

2019

Developed a head-to-head tank fight game with AI-controlled enemies, pathfinding, and an advanced control system in UE4.

More information: https://cesarmolto.github.io/battle-tank.html

ROOM MAKER VR

Graphics programmer, Designer and Project Manager

2017 - 2018

Led a 4 people team into programming and designing a Virtual Reality scenario editor with Unity 3D and Oculus hardware.

More information: https://cesarmolto.github.io/room-maker.html